[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which blood type is called the universal recipient?", "correct_answer": "AB", "incorrect_answers": ["O", "A", "B"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This engineer, called the father of supercomputing, has been credited with creating the supercomputer industry.", "correct_answer": "Seymour Gray", "incorrect_answers": ["Charles Babbage", "Bill Gates", "Steve Jobs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There have been numerous debates over whether this moon, discovered in 1978, should be considered a satellite or a separate planet.", "correct_answer": "Charon", "incorrect_answers": ["Nereid", "Nix", "Umbriel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What  year did Alfred Hitchcock become a US citizen?", "correct_answer": "1956", "incorrect_answers": ["He never became a citizen", "1946", "1965"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What song by Destinys Child was featured in the soundtrack of Romeo Must Die ?", "correct_answer": "Perfect Man", "incorrect_answers": ["Sexy Daddy", "Bootylicious", "Survivor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is Willy Wonka singing a hip-hop song in Epic Movie?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term Siamese twins comes from the famous case of Eng and Chang Bunker, who were conjoined twin brothers, born in Thailand in 1811.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What American singer and actress performed the theme song of the James Bond movie You Only Live Twice?", "correct_answer": "Nancy Sinatra", "incorrect_answers": ["Mary Hopkin", "Sylvia Anderson", "Julie Driscoll"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the one-eyed weasel that makes a debut appearance in Ice Age: Dawn of the Dinosaurs?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Bu", "Buck", "Buckminster"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of animal is Mr. Jingles who was resurrected by John in the 1999 movie The Green Mile?", "correct_answer": "Mouse", "incorrect_answers": ["Dog", "Cat", "Canary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How old does Star Wars character Yoda say he is?", "correct_answer": "900 years", "incorrect_answers": ["400 years", "100 years", "500 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ice caps and glaciers are the second largest water reservoirs on Earth after oceans. What percent of the planet\u2019s water do they hold?", "correct_answer": "2 %", "incorrect_answers": ["18 %", "10 %", "5 %"]}]